A Guide to the Papers of Robert Frost, 1873-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II. Letters
  - Subseries A. Correspondence of Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
    - Subseries 2. Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
      - Lesley Frost to Delphis Gardner, 1915 December 20; ALS, 2 p. on 1 l. (Box 9)
        Frost thanks Gardner for his magazine "Reign" that had he sent which included some of his drawings and poems. She describes the Christmas season around her home, her desire for skis, and the beautiful landscape filled with snow laden firs. Of note is Frost's description of a buck and doe sighting on one of her walks that was likely the inspiration for Robert Frost's poem "Two Look at Two" according to Lesley Lee Francis in her article "Robert Frost: Franconia Christmas 1915."
      - Mary Gardner to Lesley Frost, 1919 February 1; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Mentioning industrial unrest, a future lecture tour in the United States by her husband, and the reconstruction part of the peace program.
      - M[ary] Gardner to Lesley Frost, n.d.; APCS (Box 9)
        Concerning the mountains and area she was visiting.
      - Dorothy Haines to Lesley Frost, 1915 March 8; ALS, 6 p. (Box 9)
        With family news, noting that she was taking first aid as part of the English war effort.
      - Dorothy Haines to Lesley Frost, 1915 July 16; ALS, 7 p. (Box 9)
        Describing a trip to her childhood home and stories about her life, a visit from Mr. [Edward] Thomas and the Abercrombies.
      - [Dorothy Haines]to Marjorie Frost, 1915 July 29; APC, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Concerning Clifton Downs, Bristol.
      - Dorothy Haines to Carol Frost, 1915 July 29; APCS (Box 9)
        Showing a picture of her childhood home, "On the Downs, Bristol"
      - Dorothy Haines to Lesley Frost, [1915] December 16; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Describing the various chores performed by women in the English war effort.
      - Dorothy Haines to Lesley Frost, 1916 December 11; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Describing the qualifications for nurses in England, approval of the new English government, a visit by Catherine Abercrombie and Edward Thomas, letters censored by the postmaster, and the publication of Eleanor Farjeon's book.
      - Dorothy Haines to Eleanor [sic] [Frost], 1918 October 2; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Discussing Catherine Abercrombie's health and visit, Lascelles Abercrombie's unfinished plays, news of Merfyn Thomasentering the army, and Edward Thomas' second book of poems.
      - Dorothy Haines to Lesley Frost, 1924 July 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Inquiring if Robert Frost ever received any of her husband Jack's letters, and if the Frosts planned to visit England again.
      - W. J. Harding, "The Capt[ain]," to Marjorie [Frost], 1913 September 15; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Acknowledging her letter.
      - W. J. Harding to Irma [Frost], 1913 September 18; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Thanking her for her letter in which she asked him to be the captain on a ship the children wanted to build.
      - W. J. H[arding], "the Capt[ain]," to Carol [Frost], 1913 September 18; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Referring to the Frost children's sea trip from Scotland.
      - Beulah Huckins to Lesley Frost, 1912 December 16; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Writing of her family, her illness, and her Christmas plans.
      - Beulah Huckins to Lesley Frost, 1915 March 3; ALS, 2 p (Box 9)
        Asking her to visit and telling her about a school play.
      - Beulah [Huckins]to Lesley Frost, 1915 March 16; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Writing about a play and a possible visit by Lesley.
      - Beulah [Huckins]to Lesley Frost, 1916 July 14; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Concerning her visit to Meredith, New Hampshire, and other activities.
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Lynch, 1912 October 25; ALS (copy), 8 p. (Box 9)
        Describing the journey of the Frost family to England, and their cottage at Beaconsfield.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley Frost, 1913 September 12; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Asking her not to tell anyone that she wanted to know the name of Mr. [Robert] Frost's book.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley [Frost], 1914 January 9; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Describing a party.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley [Frost], 1914 April 12; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Describing two rainbows.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley Frost, 1915 December 31; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Mentioning Christmas presents and the work of her parents.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley Frost, 1919 February 23; ALS, 6 p. (Box 9)
        Mentioning the mutiny of demobilized British soldiers, annoyance regarding Woodrow Wilson, labor disturbances, and the lack of good plays.
      - Lucy [Mair]to Lesley Frost, 1924 June 7; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Congratulating her on the opening of her new book shop, and mentioning her own work at the League of Nations Unionand the Liberal Party.
      - Lucy Mair to Lesley Frost, n.y. December 30; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Describing her Christmas presents.
      - John Masefield to Robert Frost, 1916 March 21; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 9)
        Thanking him for his kind letter and expressing his enjoyment of North of Boston.
      - May Ribbons to Lesley Frost, 1917 April 5; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 9)
        Concerning family news.
      - Amy [Smith]to Lesley Frost, 1915 February 10; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 9)
        Telling her good-bye and enclosing a letter from "Anne" and seven "notes" to be opened daily while on passage home to the United States.
      - Flora [Smith]to Lesley [Frost], [1913] October 28; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Describing her school and holiday plans.
      - Flora [Smith]to Lesley [Frost], 1913 December 30; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Describing her visit to a circus, including an autograph poem "The Flint Arrow-head," and enclosing a photograph of her father, [James Cruickshank] Smith, and two poems.
      - Bronwen [Thomas] to Irma and Lesley [Frost], n.d. Tues; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Thanking them for sending the magazine ["The Bouquet"].
      - Edward Thomas to Lesley [Frost], 1914 December 30; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Thanking her for her picture of the "Gallows" and offering her the use of an enclosed poem (carbon) "October" in her next magazine.
      - Edward Thomas to Lesley Frost, 1915 October 28; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 9)
        Writing of camp in London, [ Ontario, Canada] and possibly receiving a communion in a Welsh regiment, and discussing his family's life at Steep, [ Petersfield, Hants, Nova Scotia, Canada].
      - Helen Thomas to Lesley Frost, 1916 May 8; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 9)
        Mentioning family news, especially of a visit by Edward Thomas, the Irish rebellion, and World War I; and, enclosing two photographs of herself, Merfyn, Bronwen, and Myfanwy Thomas.
      - Merfyn [Thomas]to Lesley [Frost], n.d.; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Concerning several items he is sending for the magazine, ["The Bouquet"], and a bike trip with his father.
      - Merfyn [Thomas]to Lesley [Frost], n.d.; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Apologizing for keeping the magazine too long and sending a story for the July issue.
      - Kathleen Morrison to Earle Bernheimer, [1940] January 13; Telegram (Box 9)
        Informing Bernheimer that Robert Frost is recovering from a minor operation and will send him a signed copy of ["Twilight"?] insured by express on Monday.
      - Robert Frost to Earle Bernheimer, 1940 February 1; Telegram (Box 9)
        While still in the hospital, Frost expresses concern over the best way to send him a copy of ["Twilight"?] and asks if he would like to come get it at Casa Marina Key West.
      - Delphis Gardner to Lesley Frost, 1916 September 13; ALS (Box 9)
        Discusses school at Southwold and his family. Mentions war-related matters, including Phyllis doing engineering drawing on motor paper as a form of war work, having a petrol permit for six gallons per month, and sending the Rein war Numer.
      - Delphis Gardner to Lesley Frost, n.d.; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions going to Scotland.
      - Mary Gardner to Robert Frost, 1913 May 28; ALS (copy) (Box 9)
        Questions the distinction between being a major or minor force in poetry and relating that "America is waiting for a poet to indicate to her her true ambitions..." and asks if that poet is him. She mentions the [Walt] Whitman that he read and Ezra Pound. (From the original in Dartmouth College Library).
      - Mary Gardner to [Robert Frost], 1913 June 13; ALS (copy) (Box 9)
        Concerns some of his drawings, her friend Mrs. Mair, and the English review of A Boy's Will. (From the original in the Dartmouth College Library).
      - Mary Gardner to Robert Frost, 1913 August 3; ALS (copy) (Box 9)
        Apologizes for the possibility of offending him at the club and relating personal news. (From the original in the Dartmouth College Library).
      - Mary Gardner to [Elinor] Frost, 1913 December 15; ALS (copy) (Box 9)
        Suggests that she and Mrs. Muir take care of their little ones so that the Frosts can have a little honeymoon. (From the original in the Dartmouth College Library).
      - Beulah Huckins to Lesley Frost, 1912 October 30; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions paper dolls, tether ball, playmates, and school.
      - Beulah Huckins to Lesley Frost, 1915 March 28; ALS (Box 9)
        Inquires about the paper ("The Bouquet") that she had mentioned.
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1913 September 10; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions photographs taken at Kingsbarns.
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1914 October 10; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions Edinburgh and Arthur Seat and soldiers being there.
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1916 June 16; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions news of the war and chickenpox in the family, and discusses at length their musical festival for Whitsunday.
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1917 January 13; TLS (copy) (Box 9)
        Refers to peoples' opinions on the war, giving news of the Smiths, inquiring of her Literary Society and whether she writes poetry. She relates the war work of her mother at the Ministry of Food as private secretary to Lord Will[iam Henry] Beveridge.
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1918 January 15; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions the Smiths' return to Edinburgh and her mother being made an officer of the British Empire, and encloses a typed copy of a poem beginning "I planned for a roadside arbor..."
      - Lucy [Mair] to Lesley Frost, 1919 January 1; ALS (Box 9)
        Describes some of the activities celebrating Armistice Day in London; mentions her family's war efforts; her cousing Lord Will[iam Henry] Beveridge and the economic problems in Vienna, Austria, President Woodrow Wilson making a visit to London, and peoples' opinions on King George and on President Wilson.
      - "Flora MacDonald" [Amy Smith] to Lesley Frost, 1913 September 9; ALS (Box 9)
        Comments on Lesley's trip to Edinburgh where she saw regiments of soldiers and met a great granddaughter of Flora MacDonald.'
      - Amy Smith to Lesley Frost, 1914 February 4; ALS (Box 9)
        Writes that she is preparing for school examinations and commenting on the story "The Valley of Mist" and William Butler Yeats' The Land of Heart's Desire.
      - Amy Smith (or Flora) to Lesley Frost, 1914 June 23; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions her activities including playing in a concert in St. Andrews Hall and taking photographs; accepts her offer to join her magazine ( The Bouquet ); discusses the activities at their school's summer picnic; and, encloses two of her poems, "The Passing of Elaine" and "Ode to Late October."
      - Amy Smith (or Flora, or Jemima Dowsabella...) to Lesley Frost, 1914 October 27; ALS (Box 9)
        Mentions the Frosts' trip to Edinburgh and encloses her poem, "October Weather."
      - Anne Smith to Lesley Frost, 1914 October 21; ALS (Box 9)
      - Anne Smith to Lesley Frost, 1914 November 26; ALS (Box 9)
      - Anne Smith to Lesley Frost, n.y. December 20; ALS (Box 9)
      - Edith Philip Smith to Lesley Frost, 1914 July 27; ALS (Box 9)
        Comments favorably on The Bouquet and inquires whether she invents "The Usual Story Reversed."
      - Edith Smith (mother) to Lesley Frost, 1914 November 4; ALS (Box 9)
        Relates a humorous story about their little Anne and attending church by herself.
      - Edith Philip Smith to Lesley Frost, 1914 November 14; ALS (Box 9)
        Comments on the Scotch language and not being able to write of the war.
      - [Merfyn Thomas] essay, "A Bicycle Race.", [1914]; ALS (Box 9)
        Written for Lesley Frost's The Bouquet.
      - Merfyn Thomas to Irma Frost, 1915 March 19; ALS (Box 9)
        Writes that he has heard from Bronwen [Thomas] and inquires about a good book on baseball.
      - Merfyn Thomas to Lesley Frost, 1915 April 3; ALS (Box 9)
        Describes his project of making a model sawmill with his school partner, Heman Chase, and getting used to living in East Alstead, New Hampshire.
      - Merfyn Thomas to Lesley Frost, [1915]; ALS (Box 9)
        Sends a cypher for The Bouquet and comments that his friend, Heman Chase, probably will not contribute to the magazine.
      - R[obert] C[alverley] Trevelyan to Robert Frost, 1917 December 26; ALS (Box 9)
        Encloses the first installment as his share of the profits on the sale of The Annual of New Poetry and comments on the book; relates news of Wilfred W. Gibson and family.
      - Information re Correspondents of Lesley Frost, including Gardner, Mair and Smith family members, 1988, n.d.; 2 items (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to David Morton, 1925 September 11; APCS (Box 9)
        Re his teaching of poetry.
      - Robert Frost to William Stanley Braithwaite, 1958 August 11; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Expressing gratitude that he wishes him [Frost] to be included in the next anthology.
      - [William] Stanley [Braithwaite]to Margaret [Carpenter], 1958 August 15; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Enclosing Robert Frost's letter of August 11th. Commenting at length on "Frost's heart and friendly cooperations" concerning the anthology.
      - Robert Frost to [William Stanley] Braithwaite, [1958]; ANS (Box 9)
        Concerning writing out a poem for Miss [Margaret] Carpenter.
      - Robert Frost to [William Stanley] Braithwaite, [ca. 1958]; ANS (Box 9)
        Written on first page of five-page printed poem, "Kitty Hawk," with cover sheet inscribed with title by Frost. Commenting on dedicating poems to those he knows intimately, and promising to copy out one of his poems for the [anthology] display.
      - James Southall Wilson to Robert Frost 1928 September. 18, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lambert Davis 1934 November.14, ALS, 2 p. on 1 l. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lambert Davis 1936 February.16, ALS, 2 p. on 1 l. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lambert Davis 1936 March.3, ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Archibald Bolling Shepperson 1942 February. 1., ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lambert Davis n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
  - Subseries B. Correspondence of Lesley Frost Ballantine
    - Lesley Frost Ballantine to Cornelia Barrett, 1972 September 19; APCS (Box 9)
    - Lesley Frost Ballantine to Cornelia Barrett, 1972 September 28; APCS (Box 9)
    - Lesley [Frost Ballantine]to [Clifton] Waller [Barrett], 1972 December 2; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
    - Lesley [Frost Ballantine]to Cornelia [Barrett], 1974 February 18; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
    - Lesley Lee Zimic to Mr. and Mrs. C[lifton] Waller Barrett, together with a copy of Mrs. Zimic's resume and a letter of recommendation, 1974 February 19; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 9)
    - Ronald Bieganowski, Marquette University, to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1978 September 27; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Presenting a copy of his doctoral dissertation on Robert Frost and an article derived from it.
    - Ronald Bieganowski, Marquette University, to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1978 October 4; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Sending her a copy of his Robert Frost article based on his dissertation, TMs, "Robert Frost's Sense of Place and Religious Consciousness."
    - Linda Bourgault-Symington, Plymouth State College, to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1979 February 23; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Inviting her to ceremonies including presentation of the seventh Robert Frost Contemporary American Award to Dr. J. Duane Squires.
    - Linda Bourgault-Symington, Plymouth State College, to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1979 May 3; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Re attending the ceremonies honoring J. Duane Squires.
    - Aaron Copland, MacDowell Colony, to Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Ballantine, 1962 October 18; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Inviting them to a program of Robert Frost readings and his being awarded the MacDowell Medal.
    - Mrs. Kerry F. Harris to Lesley Frost Ballantine, n.d.; TLS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      Asking permission to quote from material held by the Frost estate for her thesis, and enclosing a copy of an essay about Robert Frost; and asking for a recommendation for a fellowship/scholarship.
    - Edward Connery Lathem, Associate Librarian, Dartmouth College, to Alfred C. Edwards, of Holt, Rinehart and Wilson, 1966 July 7; TLS (copy), 1 p. (Box 9)
      Asking him to forward Robert Frost keepsakes to members of the Frost family.
    - C. Scott Parker, Amherst College, to Mrs. Irma (Frost) Cone, 1963 March 23; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 9)
      Sending her a copy of the minutes adopted by the faculty in memory of Robert Frost, with two enclosures.
    - J. Duane Squires to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1979 April 30; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 9)
      Thanking her for attending a dinner in honor of Robert Frost.
    - Joan St. Crane to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1972 November 3; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Concerning Mrs. Ballantine's preface to Crane's book, Robert Frost: A Descriptive Catalogue of Books and Manuscripts in the Clifton Waller Barrett Library, University of Virginia.
    - Joan St. Crane to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1973 December 27; TLS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Thanking her for Going on Two, and a photograph of the Ann Arbor Frost house.
    - Lesley Frost Ballantine to [Clifton] Waller Barrett, 1974 June 15; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      Expressing her admiration for the bibliography of Robert Frost.
    - Lesley Frost [Ballantine] to "the Franconia Place", 1977 April 15; ALS (copy), 1 p. (Box 9)
      Regarding the preservation of the Frost house at Franconia.
  - Subseries C. General Correspondence
    - George Dillon to Robert W. Stallman, 1947 May 24; TLS, 1 p. (Box 10)
    - Wade Van Dore to Harry Meacham, 1968 March 16; TLS (Box 10)
    - Margaret M. Parks, professor of chemisty, University of Rhode Island, with various colleges and universities, concerning the honorary degrees that Robert Frost received, 1962-1963; Letters (Box 10)
      A list of honorary degrees by date is included: Amherst College, Amherst, Massachusetts (1962-1963); Bates College, Lewiston, Maine (1962); Boston University, Boston, Massachusetts (1963); Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine (1962); California, University of, Berkeley, California (1962); Cambridge University, Cambridge, England (1963); Cincinnati, University of, Cincinnati, Ohio (1963); Colby College, Waterville, Maine (1963); Colgate University, Hamilton, New York (1962); Colorado, University of, Boulder, Colorado (1962); Columbia University, New York, New York (1962); Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire (1962- 1963); Dublin University, Dublin, Ireland (1963); Duke University, Durham, North Carolina (1962-1963); Durham, University of, Durham, England (1962); Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts (1962); Hebrew University, Jerusalem, Israel (1963); Kenyon College, Gambier, Ohio (1963); Marlboro College, Marlboro, Vermont (1962); Massachusetts, University of, Amherst, Massachusetts (1962); Miami University, Oxford, Ohio (1963); Miami, University of, Coral Gables, Florida (1963); Michigan, University of, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1963); Middlebury College, Middlebury, Vermont (1962-1963); New Hampshire, University of, Durham, New Hampshire (1962); New York University, New York, New York (1963); North Carolina, University of, Chapel Hill, North Carolina (1963); Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio (1963); Oxford University, Oxford, England (1963); Pennsylvania, University of, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (1962); Princeton University, Princeton, New Jersey (1962); St. Lawrence University, Canton, New York (1962); Syracuse University, Syracuse, New York (1963); Tufts University, Medford, Massachusetts (1963); Vermont, University of, Burlington, Vermont (1962); Wesleyan University, Middletown, Connecticut (1962); Williams College, Williamstown, Massachusetts (1962); Wooster College, Wooster, Ohio (1963); Wyoming, University of, Laramie, Wyoming (1963); Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut (1962).
    - John S. Van E. Kohn to [Clifton] Waller [Barrett], 1976 August 22; ALS, 2 p. (Box 10)
    - Clarence R. Decker to William Jay Smith w/AMsS on verso, "Robert Frost: The Road Taken," by Smith, 1957 December 23; TLS (Box 10)
    - Lawrance Thompson, Frost's biographer, to "Margie" [Mrs. Louis H. Cohn], 1954 June 10; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 10)
      Concerning his description of "the little Frost notebook," which he enclosed on a separate typed leaf, and thanking her for the opportunity of examining it.
    - Ray Nash to Earl Bernheimber, 1944 Memorial Day; TLS, 1 p. (Box 10)
      Concerning proofs of The Meeting of Mounted Men. 6261-bi
- Series III. Miscellaneous
  - Marriage certificate for William P. Frost and Belle Moodey [sic] [Isabelle Moodie], 1873 March 18; Document (Box 11)
  - Program, "The Department of Dramatic Arts of Amherst Collegepresents Four One-Act Plays" including an adaptation of Robert Frost's poem "Snow" for the stage. Signed at top by Frost, 1942; TMsS (copy), 2 p. (Box 11)
  - "Christmas (marked out) Season's Greetings for the year 1943 from Earl[e] J. Bernheimer," with autograph notation "First Proof--with new corrections. E. J. Bernheimer." Includes reproduction of first draft of Act I of "The Guardeen", Proof (Box 11)
  - Bread Loaf Theatre: An Evening of Robert Frost-- "The Hill Wife" and "A Masque of Reason," sent to Earle Bernheimer, 1946 August 2; Playbill (Box 11)
  - Bread Loaf Theatre: "A Masque of Mercy" and "The Search for Death," inscribed "To Earle [J. Bernheimer] from Robert [Frost] Ripton September 10 - 1948", 1948 August 6; Playbill (Box 11)
  - List of people in Robert Frost's Philosophy 8 class, with autograph notes on back, n.d.; TMs & AMs, 2 p. (Box 11)
  - "First Speller, Lesley's Speller," probably made by Elinor Frost. Bound, 1904 March 1; TMs, 7 p. (Box 11)
  - Descriptions of letters [by William P. Frost], written on front, n.d.; Envelope (Box 11)
  - Picture postcards of Joseph W. Ballantine's painting, "A Japanese Scene," Burr Artists, New York, New York. Photograph by Charles Anderson, PCs (Box 11)
  - Poetry Society of America: 64th Annual Dinner celebrating the birth of Robert Frost, Honorary President, 1974; Program (Box 11)
  - Poetry Society of America48th anniversary dinner, Robert Frost, honorary president, 1958 January 16; Invitation (Box 11)
  - Henry Holt and Company, Inc.to Mrs. Lesley Frost Ballantine, to attend the 85th birthday dinner in honor of Robert Frost, 1959 March 26; Invitation (Box 11)
  - The MacDowell Colony: Robert Frost reading of his poetry and his being awarded the Edward MacDowell Medal, ante 1962 November 8; Invitation (Box 11)
  - The MacDowell Colony: Robert Frost reading of his poetry and his being awarded the MacDowell Medal. [four copies; two with ink sketches of Robert Frost], 1962 November; Program (Box 11)
  - " Robert Frost, Lectures and Poetry Readings, 1921-1962", ca. 1962; Copy (Box 11)
  - Poetry Society of America53rd anniversary dinner, Robert Frost, honorary president, 1963 January 17; Invitation (Box 11)